A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Activities, Series A FA338
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Inc.
  - Special Studies Project
    - Minutes, Overall Panel Meeting, 1957 (Box 105, Folder 870)
      Lists of members of overall panel and subpanels, agendas for each panel, papers to be written and by whom.
    - Report, Subpanel I, "The American National Purpose in the World Environment" (draft copy), May 18, 1957 (Box 105, Folder 871)
    - Report I, "The Mid-Century Challenge to U.S. Foreign Policy" (clippings and radio reports), 1959 (Box 106, Folder 872)
    - Report II, "International Security: The Military Aspect"
      - Clippings and Radio Reports, 1958 (Box 106, Folder 873)
      - Clippings and Radio Reports, 1958 (Box 106, Folder 874)
      - Clippings and Radio Reports, 1958 (Box 106, Folder 875)
      - Clippings and Radio Reports, 1958 (Box 106, Folder 876)
      - Clippings and Radio Reports, 1958 (Box 107, Folder 877)
      - Clippings and Radio Reports, 1958 (Box 107, Folder 878)
      - Clippings and Radio Reports, 1958 (Box 107, Folder 879)
      - Clippings and Radio Reports, 1958 (Box 107, Folder 880)
      - Clippings and Radio Reports, 1958 (Box 107, Folder 881)
      - NAR Response to New York Times Editorial, 1958 (Box 107, Folder 882)
        Drafts of NAR's proposed letter to the editor by Henry A. Kissinger.
      - Summary, 1958 (Box 107, Folder 883)
      - Testimony, 1958 (Box 107, Folder 884)
        NAR's remarks before the Preparedness Subcommittee of the Senate Armed Services Committee, 1/10/58.
      - Testimony - Letters of Congratulation, Excerpts, 1958 (Box 107, Folder 885)
      - Testimony, 1958 (Box 107, Folder 886)
        NAR's remarks before the Defense Subcommittee of the House Appropriations Committee, 1/31/58.
      - Testimony, David Sarnoff, 1958 (Box 107, Folder 887)
        Before the Preparedness Subcommittee of the Senate Armed Services Committee, 1/13/58.
      - "Congressional Record", 1958 (Box 107, Folder 888)
        Copy of "Congressional Record" with Senator Prescott Bush's proposed bill for unification of the armed forces based upon conclusions presented by panel report II. Correspondence between Bush and NAR.
      - Commentary by Robert Wood Johnson, 1958 (Box 107, Folder 889)
      - New York Times Clippings, 1958 (Box 107, Folder 890)
      - Memorandum, Joint Chiefs of Staff, 1958 (Box 107, Folder 891)
        Critical analysis of panel report II. Interesting note from Donna Mitchell to Nancy Hanks.
      - Memorandum from Stacy May, 1958 (Box 107, Folder 892)
        Memo of 1/14/58 on whether Defense Dep't. budget for 1959 includes increases recommended by panel report II.
    - Report III, "Foreign Economic Policy for the Twentieth Century" - Clippings, 1958 (Box 107, Folder 893)
    - Report III, "Foreign Economic Policy for the Twentieth Century" - Clippings, 1958 (Box 107, Folder 894)
    - Report III, "Foreign Economic Policy for the Twentieth Century" - Memorandum from Stacy May, 1958 (Box 107, Folder 895)
      Memo of 10/5/60 with suggested changes in report.
    - NOT USED (Box 108, Folder 896)
    - Report IV, "The Challenge to America" - "A Decade Later and a Look Ahead", 1967 (Box 108, Folder 897)
      By William F. Butler, Karen Gerard, and Al Litwak, 11/30/67, draft.
    - Report IV, "The Challenge to America" - Clippings, 1958 (Box 108, Folder 898)
    - Report IV, "The Challenge to America" - Clippings, 1958 (Box 108, Folder 899)
    - Report IV, "The Challenge to America" - Clippings, 1958 (Box 108, Folder 900)
    - Report IV, "The Challenge to America" - Letters of Congratulations, Excerpts, 1958 (Box 108, Folder 901)
    - Report V, "The Pursuit of Excellence" - Copy of Report, 1958 (Box 108, Folder 902)
    - Report V, "The Pursuit of Excellence" - General Correspondence, 1958 (Box 108, Folder 903)
      Comments, press release.
    - Report V, "The Pursuit of Excellence" - Clippings, 1958 (Box 108, Folder 904)
    - Report V, "The Pursuit of Excellence" - Clippings, 1958 (Box 109, Folder 905)
    - Report V, "The Pursuit of Excellence" - Clippings, 1958 (Box 109, Folder 906)
    - Report V, "The Pursuit of Excellence" - Clippings, 1958 (Box 109, Folder 907)
    - Report V, "The Pursuit of Excellence" - Report Summary, 1958 (Box 109, Folder 908)
    - Report VI, "The Power of the Democratic Idea" - Clippings, 1960-1961 (Box 109, Folder 909)
    - Report VI, "The Power of the Democratic Idea" - Comments and Proposals, 1960-1961 (Box 109, Folder 910)
      Excerpts from the overall panel meeting of 10/5/60.
    - Report VI, "The Power of the Democratic Idea" - Excerpts From Letters, 1960 (Box 109, Folder 911)
      Excerpts from letters commenting on the report.
    - Report VI, "The Power of the Democratic Idea" - Radio and TV Coverage, 1960 (Box 109, Folder 912)
    - Planning Committee Meetings, 1956-1959 (Box 109, Folder 913)
      Minutes and agendas.
    - Planning Committee Meetings, 1956-1959 (Box 109, Folder 914)
    - Planning Committee Meetings, 1956-1959 (Box 109, Folder 915)
    - Planning Committee Meetings, 1956-1959 (Box 109, Folder 916)
    - Planning Committee Meetings, 1960 (Box 110, Folder 917)
    - Planning Committee Meetings - Publications Proposals, 1957 (Box 110, Folder 918)
      Copies of correspondence, mainly with publishers, and memos re: publication of the reports.
    - Planning Committee Meetings - Copyright Procedures - Papers, 1957-1958 (Box 110, Folder 919)
      Lists and memos re: according permission to authors of panel reports to release their work for reprinting. Outline of final report, 6/6/57.
    - Planning Committee Meetings - Copyright Procedures - Reports, 1958 (Box 110, Folder 920)
      Certificates of copyright for subpanel reports II-V. Memos re: copyright for "The Future of the Democratic Idea."
    - Printed Materials - "Prospect for America", 1961 (Box 110, Folder 921)
      Hardcover edition of the panel reports, published by Doubleday.
    - Printed Materials - "Prospect for America" - Proposal for Updating, 1967 (Box 110, Folder 922)
      Paper on civil rights by M. T. Puryear.
    - Printed Materials - "Prospect for America" - Clippings, 1961 (Box 110, Folder 923)
      Press coverage, editorials, reviews.
    - Printed Materials - "Prospect for America" - "America at Mid-Century Series", 1958-1960 (Box 111, Folder 924)
      Reports I-VI - Copies of the six reports as printed separately by Doubleday.
    - Overall Panel Review Reports - Efferson, J. Norman, 1967 (Box 111, Folder 925)
      "Developments in Agriculture."
    - Overall Panel Review Reports - Gerard, Karen, 1967 (Box 111, Folder 926)
      "Economic Growth and Human Welfare."
    - Overall Panel Review Reports - Kissinger, Henry A., 1966-1967 (Box 111, Folder 927)
      "A Commission for America's Future," "Notes on U.S. Long Range Defense Planning."
    - Overall Panel Review Reports - Litwak, Al, 1967 (Box 111, Folder 928)
      "The U.S. Commitment to Education: Trend, '57-'67."
    - Overall Panel Review Reports - Puryear, M. T., 1967 (Box 111, Folder 929)
      "Civil Rights 1965: Updating 'Prospect for America'."
- San Francisco Bay Project, 1966, 1968 (Box 111, Folder 930)
  Letter to NAR and brochure re: Pacific Air Commerce Center.
- Society of Mayflower Descendants, State of New York, 1946-1947, 1949-1955, 1957, 1963, 1965, 1971-1974 (Box 111, Folder 931)
  NAR a life member. NAR contribution to endowment fund, 1949. Latter appeals declined.
- Soper, Frank malaria research material - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1946, 1948, 1951 (Box 111, Folder 932)
  Dr. Soper was director of Pan American Sanitary Bureau. Re: eradication of malaria, particularly in Latin America. NAR interested in malaria program for his American International Association for Social and Economic Development.
- Soper, Frank malaria research material - Reports, 1950-1951 (Box 111, Folder 933)
  Dr. Soper was director of Pan American Sanitary Bureau.
- Soper, Frank malaria research material - Printed Material, 1951 (Box 111, Folder 934)
- South America, Interests In - Correspondence, 1939-1940 (Box 112, Folder 935)
  Re: NAR's cultural, social and business interests in Latin America, including his oil interests in Venezuela.
- South America, Interests In - Notes, 1947 (Box 112, Folder 936)
  NAR's handwritten notes and outlines, on yellow pads and poster paper, re: economic development in Latin America. NOTE: This material is brittle and should be used with care!
- Special Legislative Committee on the Revision and Simplification of the Constitution of New York, 1958-1959
  Succeeded Temporary State Commission on the Constitutional Convention. NAR was chairman. Correspondence re: meetings; hiring staff; court reform problems; preparation of background studies.
  - General, 1958-1959 (Box 112, Folder 937)
  - General, 1958-1959 (Box 112, Folder 938)
  - General, 1958-1959 (Box 112, Folder 939)
  - General, 1958-1959 (Box 112, Folder 940)
- Speeches by NAR, 1932-1966
  - Index, 1959-1966 (Box 112, Folder 941)
  - Index, 1959-1966 (Box 112, Folder 942)
  - Index, 1959-1966 (Box 112, Folder 943)
  - Listings, 1932-1958 (Box 113, Folder 944)
    Includes place, date, and topic.
  - Notes, 1946-1947 (Box 113, Folder 945)
  - Drafts and Reading Copies, 1932-1965
    - 1932-1940 (Box 113, Folder 946)
    - 1932-1940 (Box 113, Folder 947)
    - 1932-1940 (Box 113, Folder 948)
    - 1932-1940 (Box 113, Folder 949)
    - 1932-1940 (Box 113, Folder 950)
    - 1932-1940 (Box 113, Folder 951)
    - 1932-1940 (Box 113, Folder 952)
    - 1932-1940 (Box 113, Folder 953)
    - 1932-1940 (Box 113, Folder 954)
    - 1932-1940 (Box 113, Folder 955)
    - 1932-1940 (Box 113, Folder 956)
    - 1932-1940 (Box 113, Folder 957)
    - 1932-1940 (Box 113, Folder 958)
    - 1932-1940 (Box 113, Folder 959)
    - 1932-1940 (Box 113, Folder 960)
    - 1932-1940 (Box 113, Folder 961)
    - 1932-1940 (Box 113, Folder 962)
    - 1932-1940 (Box 113, Folder 963)
    - 1932-1940 (Box 113, Folder 964)
    - 1932-1940 (Box 113, Folder 965)
    - 1932-1940 (Box 113, Folder 966)
    - 1932-1940 (Box 113, Folder 967)
    - 1932-1940 (Box 113, Folder 968)
    - 1932-1940 (Box 113, Folder 969)
    - 1932-1940 (Box 113, Folder 970)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 971)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 972)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 973)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 974)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 975)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 976)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 977)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 978)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 979)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 980)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 981)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 982)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 983)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 984)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 985)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 986)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 987)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 988)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 989)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 990)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 991)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 992)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 993)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 994)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 995)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 996)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 997)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 998)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 999)
    - 1941 Jan-Nov (Box 114, Folder 1000)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1001)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1002)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1003)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1004)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1005)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1006)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1007)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1008)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1009)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1010)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1011)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1012)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1013)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1014)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1015)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1016)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1017)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1018)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1019)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1020)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1021)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1022)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1023)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1024)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1025)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1026)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1027)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1028)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1029)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1030)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1031)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1032)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1033)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1034)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1035)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1036)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1037)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1038)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1039)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1040)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1041)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1042)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1043)
    - 1941 Dec-1942 (Box 115, Folder 1044)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1045)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1046)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1047)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1048)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1049)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1050)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1051)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1052)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1053)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1054)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1055)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1056)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1057)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1058)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1059)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1060)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1061)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1062)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1063)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1064)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1065)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1066)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1067)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1068)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1069)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1070)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1071)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1072)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1073)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1074)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1075)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1076)
    - 1943-1944 Mar (Box 116, Folder 1077)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1078)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1079)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1080)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1081)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1082)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1083)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1084)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1085)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1086)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1087)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1088)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1089)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1090)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1091)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1092)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1093)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1094)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1095)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1096)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1097)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1098)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1099)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1100)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1101)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1102)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1103)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1104)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1105)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1106)
    - 1944 Apr-1945 Apr (Box 117, Folder 1107)
    - 1945 Apr-1946 Jun (Box 118, Folder 1108)
    - 1945 Apr-1946 Jun (Box 118, Folder 1109)
    - 1945 Apr-1946 Jun (Box 118, Folder 1110)
    - 1945 Apr-1946 Jun (Box 118, Folder 1111)
    - 1945 Apr-1946 Jun (Box 118, Folder 1112)
    - 1945 Apr-1946 Jun (Box 118, Folder 1113)
    - 1945 Apr-1946 Jun (Box 118, Folder 1114)
    - 1945 Apr-1946 Jun (Box 118, Folder 1115)
    - 1945 Apr-1946 Jun (Box 118, Folder 1116)
    - 1945 Apr-1946 Jun (Box 118, Folder 1117)
    - 1945 Apr-1946 Jun (Box 118, Folder 1118)
    - 1945 Apr-1946 Jun (Box 118, Folder 1119)
    - 1945 Apr-1946 Jun (Box 118, Folder 1120)
    - 1945 Apr-1946 Jun (Box 118, Folder 1121)
    - 1945 Apr-1946 Jun (Box 118, Folder 1122)
    - 1945 Apr-1946 Jun (Box 118, Folder 1123)
    - 1945 Apr-1946 Jun (Box 118, Folder 1124)
    - 1945 Apr-1946 Jun (Box 118, Folder 1125)
    - 1945 Apr-1946 Jun (Box 118, Folder 1126)
    - 1945 Apr-1946 Jun (Box 118, Folder 1127)
    - 1945 Apr-1946 Jun (Box 118, Folder 1128)
    - 1945 Apr-1946 Jun (Box 118, Folder 1129)
    - 1945 Apr-1946 Jun (Box 118, Folder 1130)
    - 1946 Jul-1947 Jun (Box 119, Folder 1131)
    - 1946 Jul-1947 Jun (Box 119, Folder 1132)
    - 1946 Jul-1947 Jun (Box 119, Folder 1133)
    - 1946 Jul-1947 Jun (Box 119, Folder 1134)
    - 1946 Jul-1947 Jun (Box 119, Folder 1135)
    - 1946 Jul-1947 Jun (Box 119, Folder 1136)
    - 1946 Jul-1947 Jun (Box 119, Folder 1137)
    - 1946 Jul-1947 Jun (Box 119, Folder 1138)
    - 1946 Jul-1947 Jun (Box 119, Folder 1139)
    - 1946 Jul-1947 Jun (Box 119, Folder 1140)
    - 1946 Jul-1947 Jun (Box 119, Folder 1141)
    - 1946 Jul-1947 Jun (Box 119, Folder 1142)
    - 1946 Jul-1947 Jun (Box 119, Folder 1143)
    - 1946 Jul-1947 Jun (Box 119, Folder 1144)
    - 1946 Jul-1947 Jun (Box 119, Folder 1145)
    - 1946 Jul-1947 Jun (Box 119, Folder 1146)
    - 1946 Jul-1947 Jun (Box 119, Folder 1147)
    - 1946 Jul-1947 Jun (Box 119, Folder 1148)
    - 1946 Jul-1947 Jun (Box 119, Folder 1149)
    - 1946 Jul-1947 Jun (Box 119, Folder 1150)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1151)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1152)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1153)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1154)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1155)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1156)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1157)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1158)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1159)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1160)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1161)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1162)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1163)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1164)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1165)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1166)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1167)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1168)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1169)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1170)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1171)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1172)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1173)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1174)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1175)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1176)
    - 1947 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 120, Folder 1177)
    - 1950 Jan-Apr (Box 121, Folder 1178)
    - 1950 Jan-Apr (Box 121, Folder 1179)
    - 1950 Jan-Apr (Box 121, Folder 1180)
    - 1950 Jan-Apr (Box 121, Folder 1181)
    - 1950 Jan-Apr (Box 121, Folder 1182)
    - 1950 Jan-Apr (Box 121, Folder 1183)
    - 1950 Jan-Apr (Box 121, Folder 1184)
    - 1950 Jan-Apr (Box 121, Folder 1185)
    - 1950 Jan-Apr (Box 121, Folder 1186)
    - 1950 Jan-Apr (Box 121, Folder 1187)
    - 1950 Jan-Apr (Box 121, Folder 1188)
    - 1950 Jan-Apr (Box 121, Folder 1189)
    - 1950 Jan-Apr (Box 121, Folder 1190)
    - 1950 Jan-Apr (Box 121, Folder 1191)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1192)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1193)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1194)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1195)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1196)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1197)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1198)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1199)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1200)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1201)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1202)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1203)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1204)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1205)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1206)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1207)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1208)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1209)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1210)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1211)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1212)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1213)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1214)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1215)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1216)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1217)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1218)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1219)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1220)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1221)
    - 1950 Jul-1951 Apr (Box 122, Folder 1222)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1223)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1224)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1225)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1226)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1227)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1228)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1229)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1230)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1231)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1232)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1233)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1234)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1235)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1236)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1237)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1238)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1239)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1240)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1241)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1242)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1243)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1244)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1245)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1246)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1247)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1248)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1249)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1250)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1251)
    - 1951 May-1951 Nov (Box 123, Folder 1252)
    - 1952 Mar-May (Box 124, Folder 1253)
    - 1952 Mar-May (Box 124, Folder 1254)
    - 1952 Mar-May (Box 124, Folder 1255)
    - 1952 Mar-May (Box 124, Folder 1256)
    - 1952 Mar-May (Box 124, Folder 1257)
    - 1952 Mar-May (Box 124, Folder 1258)
    - 1952 Jun-Oct (Box 125, Folder 1259)
    - 1952 Jun-Oct (Box 125, Folder 1260)
    - 1952 Jun-Oct (Box 125, Folder 1261)
    - 1952 Jun-Oct (Box 125, Folder 1262)
    - 1952 Jun-Oct (Box 125, Folder 1263)
    - 1952 Jun-Oct (Box 125, Folder 1264)
    - 1952 Jun-Oct (Box 125, Folder 1265)
    - 1952 Jun-Oct (Box 125, Folder 1266)
    - 1952 Jun-Oct (Box 125, Folder 1267)
    - 1952 Jun-Oct (Box 125, Folder 1268)
    - 1952 Jun-Oct (Box 125, Folder 1269)
    - 1952 Jun-Oct (Box 125, Folder 1270)
    - 1952 Jun-Oct (Box 125, Folder 1271)
    - 1952 Jun-Oct (Box 125, Folder 1272)
    - 1952 Jun-Oct (Box 125, Folder 1273)
    - 1952 Jun-Oct (Box 125, Folder 1274)
    - 1952 Jun-Oct (Box 125, Folder 1275)